

+57 3044766419

wildsrincon.netlify.app

wildsrincon.developer@gmail.com

(i) wildsrincon

wildsrincon

in wildsrincon

wrstudioweb

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript Intermediate React Intermediate

Angular Intermediate Node JS
Novice
Bootstrap

My Sql Intermediate

HTML

Intermediate

Advanced

CSS and Preprocessors Advanced

Wordpress

**Devops** Novice

Intermediate

Linux
Intermediate

Bash Intermediate

#### **LANGUAGES**

English B1 Level Spanish Native

## **HOBBIES**

Football

Travelling

Watching TV

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

EFSET English Certificate 49/100 (B1 Intermediate) EF SET

November 2020

For more information, check out **Cousera Bootstrap** 

Professional Web Development

CodigoFacilito

CodigoFacilito

For more information, check out rxresu.me

Javascript Professional

June 2020

May 2020

For more information, check out rxresu.me

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4

and Tools: Bootstrap 4 June
The Hong Kong University of Science and
Technology

For more information, check out **Cousera Bootstrap** 

# **Wilder Rincon Iriarte**

Full Stack Software Developer

Wilder Rincon is Full Stack Software Developer focused on Javascript technologies, Wilder is a web developer for more than 5 years of experience developing websites with Wordpress CMS and web apps. He is self-taught, face new challenges and be in continuous learning.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Sempli

Fullstack Software Developer

(September 2020 - October 2020)

Tropicode Team Capstone project to develop a first solution approach in Machine Learning to Sempli company. \*\*Experience: data cleaning/treatment with Anaconda and Python, landing page layout design, and practicing infrastructure deployment as code with SAM aws services. \*\* Repository's owner is Sempli company and it has private access \*\*

#### WR Studio Web

Freelance Web Developer

(January 2013 - December 2019)

- Development Web sites, web-apps and mobile application
- Management and support of websites (Content Management System, Availability of portals)
- Customer support.

#### Safe SAS

Frontend Developer

(January 2016 - December 2016)

(January 2020 - November 2020)

- Development Web sites, web-apps and mobile application
- Management and support of websites (Content Managers, Availability of portals)
- · Customer support.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Holberton School, Colombia

**Bootcamp** Software Engineer

Software Engineering Specialty and achieved a much more thorough education in the underlying theory, concepts, and science behind more complex programming. It was here that I discovered my passion for scalable application programming (web and mobile), the security behind computer and application systems, and found that I have a knack for understanding complex algorithms.

# SENA, Barranguilla, Colombia

(January 2003 - June 2006)

**Higher School** Networks Administration Technology

Acquired skills in configuring active network equipment, general data networking topics and computer network administration.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Github Battle**

https://github-battle-wr.netlify.app/

(December 2020 - December 2020)

Project build with React and React Router, consuming API Github and deploy production and CI/CD with Netlify.

Funny game of battle Github profiles.

# **Customer classification Machine Learning**

(September 2020 - December 2020)

Tropicode Team Capstone project to develop a first solution approach in Machine Learning to Sempli company. \*\*Experience: data cleaning/treatment with Anaconda and Python, landing page layout design, and practicing infrastructure deployment as code with SAM aws services. \*\* Repository's owner is Sempli company and it has private access \*\*

# Adopt Me

https://adopt-me-wr.vercel.app

(August 2020 - December 2020)

Adopt Me , a free and open-source app built in with React JS works for you. A few of the important features that make it awesome are API Consuming, the app is connected to an animal adoption service that works only for the USA.

For more information, check out rxresu.me

## **Angular Weather App**

https://weather-app-66cf5.web.app/

(June 2020 - December 2020)

Angular App built in Angular 9, API consuming Open Weather API, weather forecast for next five days, use geolocation service for show your location.

#### Robofriends

https://robofriends-wr.netlify.app/

(November 2019 - December 2020)

React App robot search engine, use API Robohash for the import data.